## **Braian Orona**

**Back-End Developer** 

San Juan, Argentina (GMT-3) (+549) 2644850353 braianorona@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/braianorona/

Back-End Developer with +3 years of experience in web applications with **Java** and **Node.js** for building REST microservices with projects for public and private entities. Acquainted with Front-End with Angular and React. Looking for professional growth and new challenges. I consider myself a technology and programming enthusiast. My goal is to play a role in a software company and add value with my knowledge.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **MobyDigital**

Ssr Back-End Developer — July, 2023 - Present

• Payment architecture project with banks

Tech Stack: Java, Spring Framework, Microservices, Maven, MySQL, Kafka, AWS, Hibernate, Swagger

#### **Freelance**

Co-Founder | Back-End Developer — June, 2021 - Present

Freelance development for clients, from product requirements and architecture to final development.
Tech Stack: Java, Spring Framework, Maven, Hibernate, JavaScript, TypeScript, Sequelize, TypeORM, Express, Microservices, SQL, NoSQL, Swagger, GIT, Docker

### **Galicia Bank**

Ssr Back-End Developer — March, 2023 - July, 2023

Enterprise architecture project for the customer recovery business
Tech Stack: Java, Spring Framework, Microservices, Maven, MySQL, OpenShift, Jenkins Hibernate, Swagger, GIT, GitHub

#### **Folcode**

**Ssr Back-End Developer** — August, 2021- March, 2023

• I greatly increased sales by developing an API that allows the management of an e-learning platform with international payments and microservices for an international client.

**Tech Stack**: Java, Spring Framework, Microservices, Maven, MySQL, Eureka, Liquibase, Hibernate, AWS, Swagger, GIT, Jira, BitBucket, Docker, Keycloak.

• I significantly increased the efficiency of campaigns by implementing a third-party API for a marketing platform of the government of San Juan, Argentina.

**Tech Stack**: Java, Spring Framework, Microservices, Maven, MySQL, Javascript, TypeScript, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Liquibase, Sequelize, Hibernate, AWS, Swagger, GIT, Jira, BitBucket, Mailchimp

## **Folcademy**

Back-End Developer — June, 2021 - December, 2021

• I facilitated the process of making donations by creating an API for donor and donation management with Mercadopago and firebase integration for the NGO Scholas Occurrentes which impacted thousands of people.

Tech Stack: Java, Spring Framework, Maven, MySQL, Firebase, Hibernate, GIT, Jira, BitBucket

Back-End Mentor — May, 2022 - October, 2022

• I reduced the learning curve of a Bootcamp by mentoring four junior developers, assuming the role of leader and consultant in the area of Back-End with Java that participated in 2 different NGOs.

Tech Stack: Java, Spring Framework, Maven, MySQL, Hibernate, GIT, Jira, BitBucket

# **Braian Orona**

Back-End Developer

San Juan, Argentina (GMT-3) (+549) 2644850353 <u>braianorona@gmail.com</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/braianorona/

## **SKILLS**

**Programming Languages:** Advanced: Java (8, 11, 17), Javascript, TypeScript; Intermediate: C, C++, C#, HTML, CSS; Basic: Kotlin.

**Frameworks Tools:** Advanced: Spring Framework, Maven, Hibernate, Node.js, Express; <u>Basic:</u> React.js, Angular.js, .NET. **Data Base:** Advanced: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MariaDB, MongoDB; Intermediate: Firebase.

**Tools:** Git, Jira, BitBucket, Postman, MySQL Workbench, Discord, Slack, AWS, XAMPP, Kafka, Figma, Swagger, OpenShift, Jenkins

Methodologies: Agile, Scrum, Kanban

Languages: Advanced: English; Native: Spanish.

## **EDUCATION**

Universidad Nacional de San Juan - San Juan, Argentina. Bachelor's degree in computer science, 2017 - Present.